LAUGHING MAN FANSUBS
Angels and demons were circling over me,
Crossing a brambly path of stars and milky ways.
He who does not perceive his calling,
does not know true happiness.
Watch in awe! Watch in awe!
Flying in glory, Flying in glory
I am calling, calling now. Spirits rise and falling.
To be with you longer
Calling, calling...
in the depth of longing
To stay myself longer
The flow may swallow you, flying in glory
What are you gonna do?
I'm going to show them fear.
For that, the population of
earth will decrease by one.
But it hardly matters.
Perfect
Day
For
A
Jungle
Cruise
...the cause is unknown.
As for the number of people...
Excuse me, Public Safety Section 9.
You got my message, right?
Batou, how is it?
The decay is awful.
Even a veteran inspector couldn't see
at a glance how long she's been dead.
Not that, I'm asking what you think of it.
Of... course...
That was rough...
That's why I told you to look at the monitor.
Batou, that's enough.
Togusa, take it.
In the past two months,
there have been five murder cases in the city.
Adding the family of four killed today
makes that six, for a total of 12 people.
The common link is that in every case the skin on the
victim's upper body was removed in the shape of a t-shirt.
The results of the autopsies indicate a high probability
that the victims were skinned alive and then left to die.
He's nuts.
What does the profiler make of it?
Nothing, yet.
Is it possible that this is the work of an anarchist
terrorist, or a ritual for some new cult?
No, there's no possibility that this is the work of
a religiously or politically motivated criminal.
Then could it be someone from the
sex crimes past-offenders list?
It's not a question of the criminal's perversion.
He's not getting any pleasure our of these crimes.
What do you base that on?
If there's anything there, it's obligation.
Could there even be a serial murderer like that?
We were called, so there must
be new information, right chief?
Marco Amoretti,
a former sergeant in the American Navy.
According to our information from America, it's
extremely likely that he is committing these crimes.
His service record data from the Ministry of Defence says that during
the World War, he served on the front lines of various places.
But in March of 2028,
he was dismissed at his request.
Since then, he has gone missing.
And the reason you think he's our man?
He was involved in a very similar case.
A similar case?
Yeah.
Chief, if you know so much about him,
then you've already worked it out, right?
Not quite.
Through the Ministry of Foreign Affairs,
the CIA issued a secret warrant for his arrest,
and the request for his unconditional
extradition was granted today.
Hold on, that's intervention.
Basically...
Why should we have to clean up after the CIA?
Well, we hope you'll somehow be willing to do it.
Let me introduce you.
He's just arrived from America, this is...
Satou Suzuki of the CIA.
And Watanabe Tanaka.
Thank you, thank you.
Broadcast this to hostile countries.
This one will be the worst.
It appears he was pecked by
birds until he was found.
There are signs of a fight on the ground,
so the prefecture police took back
a piece of the ground as evidence,
but there was no trace of the culprit.
I see.
Construction will begin here next month.
The crime scene will be gone.
We won't let it go for too long.
Crane viewing place.
I wonder if there are any cranes?
There aren't any cranes left
anymore, just crows now.
Hey buddy, can I ask you something?
Is there something you aren't telling us?
Yeah, I'm also interested in that.
Are you done?
When I find the guy,
it'll be his eternal farewell from this world.
Keep that in mind.
How theatrical.
Batou, Batou? Are you all right?
Yeah, it was nothing.
Hey! Don't just take the liberty
of prying into someone's head!
You're not yourself today.
Do you have a fever?
But it has nothing to do with him right?
Togusa, this is a cipher communication,
just stay silent and listen.
If Batou goes berserk while working on this case,
you need to restrain him.
Horrible! There's nothing like
canned coffee to wake you up!
Something's up, isn't it, between Batou and the suspect?
I don't know.
But he's not at his usual state of concentration.
That's true.
Understood, I will do what I can.
Ahh, I don't need caffeine.
If it tastes bad, just shut up and do some prep work.
I'm counting on you.
Understood.
This case has been approved.
We'll stop our investigation.
I'll leave the negotiation
with the prosecutor to you.
No problem.
However, since the suspect's being sought
by the CIA, this case will go unsolved.
Now, how to convince the guys in the field...
That's also included in our job, to finish it.
I have another request.
Ah, thanks.
Major, how about you and Ishikawa try
poking around this prick's organisation.
Here, thank you.
Ah, I don't have my card with me...
Roger.
Watanabe Tanaka-San.
Note: This is an obviously fake name, like John Smith
Chief, please come to
headquarters as soon as possible.
I'm in the middle of a meeting.
We've found first hand
recordings of the crime scene.
What? Where?
Well... It was being sold at a video
shop on Radio Street in New Port Akiba.
Pazu, Bouma, go to the
Electronics District immediately.
Get the story from the video store owner.
Try to remove the records from the IR System.
Roger. Chief...
Hmm, you've found out?
It seems like Watanabe was anticipating that.
This place seems fun!
Looks like we could gain some experience points here.
There's no time for any side quests.
Yes ma'am.
Pazu, secure the surrounding stores.
Bouma, get the story from the owner.
Follow the source of the footage.
Roger.
Pick up all the footage of
customers from yesterday.
Okay.
Major, I think it will all work out somehow.
Note: They're talking about hacking into the CIA
At this rate, we won't even be able
to properly knock on their back door.
They think they're keeping an eye on us, don't they?
I don't get much credit, do I.
That's why we're going to try the back
door, maybe we can find something.
Watanabe-San, it seems the footage
that was seized has arrived.
May we look at it?
Yeah, let's do that.
Then, let's go over to that booth.
Ah, over there?
I'll leave it to you.
Well then.
Bastard.
Why did that bastard purposely
distribute that kind of data?!
Because, for him, THAT is the goal.
Don't you think so, Satou-San?
I wonder what it's all about?
Before I came to Section 9, I was a Ranger.
I also have experience lurking
in the jungles of South America.
Well, what does that have to do with this data?
Don't act as if you don't know!
That kept right on going even after
you in the American Empire pulled out!
And that nightmare shows itself again.
Nightmare...?
What's this?
The criminal probably showed
the video to the victims.
You mean... so they could watch
themselves being skinned alive?
So it seems.
How cruel.
Looks like all six cases are here.
Ishikawa, did you find anything?
Yeah.
As is to be expected from the
CIA, there's strong protection,
but Fort Plug has some records left.
In the CIA files, there are many reports of
Marco undergoing psychological counseling.
Isn't there any more detailed information?
Ah, hold on hold on...
What's this file?
Project Sunset?
Project Sunset.
Since you don't know about it, I'll tell you.
During the previous war,
in order to hurt enemy morale,
the CIA came up with an operation where
agents would sneak into enemy bases,
and after gaining the trust of the locals,
kill the women and children as brutally as possible.
The codename was Project Sunset.
You call that a strategy? You must be kidding!
That kind of project never existed.
That is our country's official position.
Rumour has it that there were many cases where the soldiers
who participated in these missions became mentally ill.
Why would a person like that be on this street?
Nobody knows these kinds of things.
Guess we'll just have to look at the psychological
analysts' horoscope-like reports.
I know.
His war has yet to end.
And mine too.
I've only heard rumours before,
but I guess he really exists.
However, if his goal is to
get rid of the spirit of war,
Marco will not stop his crimes as long as he's in this
country, which is apathetic to the deaths of others.
Major, it seems Marco sold murder footage...
to a bunch of homeless people living
in the park near Radio Street.
I'll send the files of the
seven cases that we've seized.
Seven cases? Yet another victim has appeared.
Send it over, fast.
Please... stop...
NO!!
Damn it, this time the visual
information is from the victim, isn't it.
Bouma, do you know the date
and time of the original file?
Last night!
Determine the victim's
address from the voice print.
There's a chance that she's still alive.
I'm almost sorry that she's alive.
Skin regeneration technology is very advanced now.
But it will never be completely
back to the way it used to be.
Are you happy about this?
This is the monster that you
people created doing its job!
That's why we came to recycle it.
"Recycle"? You Bastard!
Stop it! Choking this bastard to death
wont help anything!
Damn it!
Don't you dare run away this time.
I won't let him get away this time.
I'll make sure to end his life.
This time?
I see. If you had disposed of him, we
wouldn't have had to come all this way.
What are you guys talking about? Hey!
Where... where is that bastard hiding?
How about asking me for advice?
That's why I've been touring
the crime scenes with you.
What can you possibly tell us?!
Hold on! What are you saying?
There's a sewer under here isn't there?
By sewer, you mean a storm drain.
Storm drain?
Yeah, it's a covered stream.
Speaking of which, there's a storm drain running under the
park where that guy was passing data to homeless people.
The path of the stream matches.
That bastard goes upstream to go commit a crime,
and then returns downstream to the city to spread it.
As you said, he's...
Underneath our feet.
You wait there! I'll hand you a body bag later.
If Marco is moving through the storm drain,
there's a good chance that
he's using it as a hideout.
Bouma, you guys stay that way,
and come into the drain from the other side.
We'll surround him and catch that bastard.
Batou, can I trust those words?
Batou?
Ugh, so damp!
Our visibility index for the
optical camouflage will go up.
Won't the gasket be corroded?
Stop talking,
you should be glad you can't smell it.
My sensor can analyse it you know.
Do you dislike it?
Your discomfort level is at 68%!
Shut up.
Hey, what's this?
It's a hidden trap for any
attack from the outside.
But of course.
We've found a hidden gun.
This humidity, the smell of decaying water...
That's right, this is definitely
the jungle where we fought before.
What are you saying to yourself?
Hey, Batou! Wait up!
Togusa, what's Batou doing?
He cut off his cyberbrain communication link.
The big guy has completely lost it.
He seriously wants to kill Marco.
What happened?
The fibre-optic cables that are installed
in the tunnel are causing interference.
Try to hook up to the circuit station
that the water department uses.
Roger.
Major, I found something outrageous
in the CIA's communication log.
These bastards didn't want to bring
back Marco from the beginning.
The order, "Make it look like an accident,
and get rid of the suspects", appeared.
That can't be!
That's what this is about, isn't it?
They knew about Batou's past...
The CIA still has Batou's records.
He saw the aftermath of the Sunset
Project when he was a Ranger.
Those bastards, we've been used!
They planned to get rid of
Batou and Marco from the start!
I have no idea what
you're trying to say.
To begin with, your illegal access
of CIA data is already a big problem.
Ishikawa, restrain him!
I'll explain the situation later.
I'm going to where Batou's at.
Hurry!
We didn't do anything.
They're still on their "Jungle Cruise",
fighting their war in the wrong time and place.
Shit.
Did you catch him?
Sorry, he got away.
You're so unreliable.
Hold up, you can't go alone.
Batou, where are you?
Marco!
Pump Room
Authorised Personnel Only
Let's finish this already!
This is the end.
Kill me.
Please, kill me.
Why?
Yeah, use that knife and peel off my skin.
Kill me.
You bastard...
You think that will release you from your mission?
What conceit!
Sorry...
My war is already over!
We only have return tickets for two.
Quit screwing around! Sorry it's
Marco instead of a body bag, huh?!
Did you think I'd shoot him?
The idea did cross my mind to try to clear my
sullied name with some archaic form of justice,
but you can't change the past so
I'll carry this with me to my grave.
This isn't his Jungle,
this is our city and I'm a police officer.
We didn't save just one person this time.
She's so cold and human
It's something humans do
She stays so cold in her soul, she's so number 9
She's incredible math
Just incredible math
And is she really human?
She says there's something new
But wake a lithium flower, just about to bloom
I smell lithium now
Smelling lithium now
How... is she what she doesn't say
She doesn't say
How is she when she doesn't suffer
I wonder what she does when she wakes up
When she wakes up